

RIAN KENJI JUNIOR YEAR STUDENT

https://portofolio-riankenji.netlify.app/ www.linkedin.com/in/rian-kenji https://github.com/RianKenji Jakarta, West Jakarta (+62)-8963-7809-472 riankenji7@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Currently a Junior majoring in Information Systems at Tarumanagara University. A quick learner with academic skills and technical understanding to excel in a variety of professions. Prepared to broaden horizons with extra knowledge and skills earned via training and experience. Always willing to assist others and contribute to team goals.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE AT IDMODZ

2019 - Present

Content Writer

- Produce well-researched content for publication online mostly about computer and games
- Use search engine optimization (SEO) strategies in writing to maximize the online visibility of a website in search results

SOUSHIN TARUMANAGARA NIHON BU - JAKARTA

2023 - Present

Secretary

- Formulate general policies in the secretarial and administrative fields of the organization as a communication and information center.
- Performed administrative tasks, document management and report development for inter-departmental use.

SOUSHIN TARUMANAGARA NIHON BU - JAKARTA

2022 - 2023

Vice Leader of Cosplay Division

- · Performed Documentation of daily activities
- Communicating with the teacher and helped in creating materials for class
- · Search and gather the necessary materials according to class needs

FORMAL EDUCATION

2021 - Present UNIVERSITAS TARUMANAGARA GPA : 3.87

Bachelor of Information Systems

2018 - 2021 **SMAN 2 JAKARTA** 87.6

High School Diploma - Social Sciences

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Travel Website

- · Built a front-end Website that allows users to look at various recommended travel location
- Using html and css

Tourist Attraction Website

- Built a front-end and back-end Website using php, apache, mysql, bootstrap, javascript
- Has a homepage, area, hotel and news pages, has a database connected to the website
- · Has a dashboard to input, edit and delete data

LANGUAGES

- English Indonesian
- Japanese (Basic)

SKILLS

- C++
- Structured Query Language (SQL)
- on dotal od quoi y Edingdago (oqE
- · HTML,CSS and Javascript
- Flutter
- Problem Solving & Critical Thinking
- Python
- Figma
- · i igiii a
- PHP
- Java
- Microsoft Office